Xian Quiyo Villanueva

0466444011

quiyoxian@gmail.com

General warehouse laborer with three-to-four years of experience in shopfitting, and cabinet making. Able to use power tools. Physically fit and able to lift heavy objects. Hard worker and excited to gain and acquire knowledge to further enhance skills in all kinds of trade. Currently working as a full-time employee in a shopfitting factory. Looking for casual-to-permanent employment in a company.

Education:

Sacred Heart International College

Certificate IV and Diploma in Human Resources

Suite 715 - 716, Level 7/343 Little Collins St, Melbourne VIC 3000

Bataan Peninsula State University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Major in Network and Web Application

Balanga City, Bataan, Philippines 2112

August 2018 – April 2020

June 2014

to

May 2018

Work Experience:

Technical support assistant

Bldg. N, SBFZ, Olongapo City, Philippines 2112

May 2017-August 2017

- Assist in fixing computer hardware and software
- Answer calls from customers and listen on their computer problems and assist them through phone call if the problem's fixable

Factory hand / Machine Operator

Melbourne Joinery and Stone / Mordialloc, VIC

June 2018 - September 2020

- Assembling and building kitchens that will be built inside the warehouse
- Control industrial machines such as; edge bander, CNC, panel saw, etc. to help with the needs in building a kitchen
- Disassemble made kitchens after its quality check from the floor managers
- Keep the warehouse's machines clean and tidy

Team Member

Woolworths Carlton, Carlton, VIC

April 2020 - November 2020

- Providing great customer service
- Assist customers on self-checkout

Assembler / General Laborer

TS & B Retail Systems

35 – 37 Kitchen Rd, Dandenong South, VIC

November 2020 - Present

- Assembling and finishing shop counters for installation
- Oversee the quality of finished products
- Assembling conveyor belts, mainly COLES conveyor belts to Self-check-outs
- Assemble new shopfitting prototypes for COLES
- Quality checking and assurance
- Metalwork

Work references:

Graham Bell

TS & B Retail Systems, 35 - 37 Kitchen Rd, Dandenong South, VIC

Floor Manager

Contact no: 0478796422

John Wood

TS & B Retail Systems, 35 – 37 Kitchen Rd, Dandenong South, VIC (Former)

Coles Manufacturing Manager (former)

Contact: 0438396072

Character reference:

Tylar David

TS & B Retail Systems

Co-worker / Factory laborer

Contact no: 0488201881